Ataraxia Shop Channel!
Say Kizuna, I'm troubled.
What's wrong Julicia?
I would like some appropriate clothing for exercise.
Isn't there anything good out there?
I have the perfect stuff for you.
The world famous Japanese cultural wear, Bloomers.
Today we've got a limited run of only 150.
Japanese people always wear these when working out.
Amazing, this is so easy to move in.
Then let's show the people just how good it is.
First the vault box.
Here I go.
Hoola hoops.
I like this.
Jump ropes.
Oh no!
Dance pole!
I'm gonna slip!
Amazing.
You can do any exercise with these.
These can be yours for 6,880 yen.
6880 Yen (tax included)
Shipping 990 Yen (tax included)
Special!
6880 Yen (tax included)
Shipping 990 Yen (tax included)
Further, a special promo.
Special!
The vault box, hoola hoop, jump rope, and dance pole will come free!
Wow, that is so nice.
But I wish there were something more exciting.
Man you are so greedy.
Then let's put this on as well.
Triangle wooden horse.
If you order within 30 minutes after this show, then we will send it to you for free.
It massages your crotch and thus makes you healthy.
Ataraxia Shop Channel!
Say Kizuna, I am troubled.
I know already, you want this don't you?
The best for swimming, a school swimsuit.
Now for a special price of 9800 yen.
9800 Yen (tax included)
Shipping 990 Yen (tax included)
And this is the classical type.
It fits me perfectly and it is so easy to swim in.
And now let's give a bit of trivia.
What is it?
Do you know?
Why is the crotch part not connected?
Isn't it to expel water that entered through the chest?
No, that is not why.
Stop touching me there.
It was made so that I can touch you like this.
Just a speculation.
Everyone's watching.
Its ok, no one is watching.
No way! Don't touch there!
Amazing!
Let's go!
I am going to leak.
That's all for today.
I've got more amazing things lined up tomorrow.
Female sushi.
That's for tomorrow.
What kind of mystery is this?